{
    "id": "4ef6bcba6c4947bbb605762fc783adfc",
    "title": "Auxiliary verbs worksheet",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "ab1b4f72f205406582e2350f43f2883a",
            "title": "Auxiliary Verbs Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "We eat that we ……………….. live.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "may",
                        "would",
                        "should"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She worked hard that she ..................... win the first prize.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "would",
                        "should"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You …………………. go only if you have the permission.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "can",
                        "will",
                        "could"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He asked whether dinner ………………….. be ready soon.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "would",
                        "should"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Even if you paid me to do so, I …………………. not support you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "would",
                        "can"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You ……………….. go out provided that you return soon.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "may",
                        "will",
                        "might"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You make such a noise that I ………………….. work.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "cannot",
                        "could not",
                        "would not"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He said that he ………………… try again.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "would",
                        "might"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The thieves stole whatever they …………………. find in the house.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "can",
                        "could",
                        "might"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… I carry this bag?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Should",
                        "Would",
                        "Will"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}